Don Walker Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Personal and Business Papers (Box 1-20)
  - Playhouse productions (Box 15)
  - Porter, Cole (Box 15)
  - Prince, Hal (Box 15)
  - Pro Musica (Box 15)
  - Properties (Box 15)
  - Publicity (2) (Box 15)
  - Ragtime blues (Box 15)
  - Ragtime blues-contracts (Box 15)
  - Ramin, Sid (Box 15)
  - RCA-Showmen album (Box 15)
  - Record notes (Box 15)
  - Red mill (Box 16)
  - Rex (Box 16)
  - Reviews-First impressions; Happy hunting; The music man (Box 16)
  - Reviews-Hazel Flagg; Maggie (Box 16)
  - Rittman, Trude (Box 16)
  - Rivera, Antonio (Box 16)
  - Robbins, Jerome (Box 16)
  - Robin, Leo (Box 16)
  - Rodgers, Richard (Box 16)
  - Rodgers and Hammerstein (Box 16)
  - Romberg, Sigmund see also Men of notes: Research (Box 16)
  - Romberg estate (Box 16)
  - Romberg recordings (Box 16)
  - Rome, Harold and Florence (Box 16)
  - Rosenstock, Milton (Box 16)
  - The Rothschilds (3) (Box 16)
  - Ruby, Harry (Box 16)
  - Russell, Rosalind (Box 16)
  - Schwartz, Arthur (Box 16)
  - Seascape (Box 16)
  - Señor discretion himself see Tepancingo
  - The seven lively arts: the gold rush (Box 16)
  - She loves me (Box 16)
  - Shenandoah (Box 17)
  - Show reviews (Box 17)
  - Silk stockings (2) (Box 17)
  - Sirmay, Doc (Box 17)
  - Sondheim, Stephen (Box 17)
  - Spring in Brazil (Box 17)
  - Stritch, Elaine (Box 17)
  - Styne, Jule (Box 17)
  - Sunny river (Box 17)
  - Tamaris, Helen (Box 17)
  - Tax data, 1964-1966 (Box 17)
  - Taxes, 1976 (Box 17)
  - Teaching inquiries (orchestration) (Box 17)
  - Telegrams see also Western Union (Box 17)
  - Ten commandments for arrangers (Box 17)
  - Tepancingo (Box 17)
  - That's the ticket (Box 17)
  - Theatre people (correspondence) (Box 17)
  - Theatre programs (Box 17)
  - A thousand clowns (Box 17)
  - A thousand clowns-contracts M-1,2 1965 Sept. 17 (Box 17)
  - A thousand clowns-costs (Box 17)
  - A thousand clowns-M-1,1 1965 Sept. 15 (Box 17)
  - A thousand clowns-M-1,3 1965 Sept. 21 -separate date (Box 17)
  - A thousand clowns-music cues and financial estimates (Box 17)
  - A thousand clowns-union (Box 18)
  - Three waltzes (Box 18)
  - Ticket school zone (Box 18)
  - A time for singing (2) (Box 18)
  - Top banana (Box 18)
  - Touch and go (Box 18)
  - Two for the show (Box 18)
  - Two's company (Box 18)
  - Unidentified show material (Box 18)
  - Union contracts and forms (Box 18)
  - United Artists Music Co. Inc. (Box 18)
  - University of Pennsylvania (Box 18)
  - The unsinkable Molly Brown (Box 18)
  - Up in Central Park (Box 18)
  - Urgent correspondence (2) (Box 18)
  - The vamp see also Delilah (Box 18)
  - Wait a minum (2) (Box 19)
  - Walker, Mrs. Thomas J. (Box 19)
  - Walker lyrics (Box 19)
  - Walker publicity (historical notes) (Box 19)
  - Warnick, Clay "Buck" (Box 19)
  - Warner-Chappell see Chappell proposition
  - Weissberger and Frosch (Box 19)
  - Western Union telegrams see also Telegrams (Box 19)
  - What a day! (Box 19)
  - What makes Sammy run?-company (Box 19)
  - What makes Sammy run?-royalty statements (Box 19)
  - The wicked, wicked city (Box 19)
  - Windy city (Box 19)
  - Winter garden (Box 19)
  - Wish you were here (Box 19)
  - Wonderful town (Box 20)
  - Wright and Forrest (Box 20)
  - Your hit parade (Box 20)
  - Ziegfeld follies (Box 20)
  - Zorba I (Box 20)
  - Zorba II (road company) (Box 20)
  - Zorba III (Box 20)
  - Zorba programs (Box 20)
- Writings (Box 21-25)
  - Bucket of Blood, circa 1958, Novel
    - Typescripts (Box-folder 21/1-4)
  - Men of Notes, circa 1984, Memoir in the form of reminiscences of composers and musicians that Walker worked with; there was to be another volume, but, according to his daughter, he didn’t have enough time to complete it
    - Dedication, Forward, 1. Fletcher (Henderson), 2. Fred (Waring) (Box-folder 21/5)
    - 1. Fletcher (Henderson), 2. Fred (Waring) (Box-folder 21/6)
    - 3. Al (Albert Goodman), 4. George M.. (Cohan), 5. Rommy (Sigmund Romberg) (Box-folder 21/7)
    - 3. Al (Albert Goodman), 4. George M.. (Cohan) (Box-folder 21/8)
    - 5. Rommy (Sigmund Romberg), 6. Frank Black (Box-folder 21/9)
    - 6. Frank Black, 7. Cole (Cole Albert Porter) (Box-folder 21/10)
    - 7. Cole (Cole Albert Porter) (Box-folder 21/11)
    - Patching pages, discards, etc. (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Early attempts at preface, forward, and introduction/1st draft of “Fletcher” (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Late discards and Rodgers and Hammerstein’s shows (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Extras (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Research (Box-folder 22/5)
  - "Music Heard, Music Written", A course Walker taught at Hunter College which he intended on turning into a book on orchestration. Includes material for a 1961 version of the book titled Technique of Orchestration
    - Final draft (Box-folder 22/6-7)
    - Final draft-extra material (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Foreward; Introduction: The plan of this work; Preface; Preface and dedication; The purpose (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Chapter I: The musical thought (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Chapter I: The musical facts of life (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Chapter II: The dimensions of music (Box-folder 22/12)
    - Chapter II: The memory of musical sounds; (miscellaneous) (Box-folder 22/13)
    - Chapter III: The instruments and the score (Box-folder 22/14)
    - Chapter III: Resultants of musical dimensions (Box-folder 22/15)
    - Chapter IV: The woodwinds (Box-folder 22/16)
    - Chapter IV: The process of musical thinking (Box-folder 22/17)
    - Chapter V: The flute family; Chapter VI: The flute family (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Chapter V: The linear instruments; Chapter V: The instruments and the score; (miscellaneous) (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Chapter VI: The oboe family (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Chapter VI: The score (Box-folder 23/4)
    - Chapter VII: The clarinet family (Box-folder 23/5)
    - Chapter VIII: The bassoon family (Box-folder 23/6)
    - Miscellaneous: research, correspondence, glossary, etc. (Box-folder 23/7)
    - Orchestration workbook, Kent Wheeler Keenan, Prentice-Hall, Inc., N.J., 1952 (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Course materials, 1957-1958
      - Organizational notes; Lecture outline; Semester I–Lecture I: The general plan; Lecture II: The musical thought; Lecture III: Factors governing musical thinking (Box-folder 23/9)
      - Semester I–Lecture IV-VII: The dimensions of musical thinking, parts I-IV; Lecture VIII-IX: Procedures of musical thinking, parts I-II (Box-folder 23/10)
      - Semester I–Lecture X-XI: Music writing procedures, parts I-II; Lecture XII: The arbitrary condition (Box-folder 23/11)
      - Outline of lectures; Semester II–Lecture I. Woodwinds I—flutes and piccolos; Lecture II: The double reeds; Lecture III: The single reeds; Lecture IV: The horn; Lecture V: The trumpet (Box-folder 23/12)
      - Semester II–Lecture VI: The trombone and tuba; Lecture VII: Strings in general; Lecture VIII: The violin and the viola; Lecture IX: The cello and the double-bass; Lecture X: The fretted strings (Box-folder 23/13)
      - Semester II–Lecture XI: Percussion; Lecture XII: Keyboard instruments; Lecture XIII: The harp; Lecture XIV: The human voice; Lecture XV: Accordion, concertina, harmonica; Final examination (Box-folder 23/14)
      - Semester III; Lecture I; Lecture II: The birth of orchestration; Lecture III: The childhood of orchestration; Lecture IV: Orchestration in adolescence; Lecture IV: Orchestration discovers life; Lecture VI: Orchestration comes of age (Box-folder 23/15)
      - Semester III–Lecture VII: Orchestration in Valhalla; Lecture VIII: Orchestration acquires principles; Lecture IX: Further “principles” of orchestration; Lecture X: The foolproof orchestration–I; Lecture XI: The foolproof orchestration–II; Lecture XII: “What idiots call Impressionism”; Lecture XIII: The Olympian virtuosos; Lecture XIV: “Orchestration without music” (Box-folder 24/1)
      - Semester IV–Lecture I-II: The electronic revolution–I-II; Lecture III-VII: Theatre orchestration I-concluded (Box-folder 24/2)
      - Semester IV–Lecture VIII: Audio orchestration; Lecture IX: Video orchestration; Lecture X: Specialized orchestration; Lecture XI: The business of orchestration; Final examination (Box-folder 24/3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 24/4)
  - 6-Piece Quintet, circa 1982-1983, Novel
    - Originals (Box-folder 24/5-8)
    - Masters, 1983 draft (Box-folder 24/9-12)
    - 1982 draft (Box-folder 25/1-4)
    - Pages in work (Box-folder 25/5)
    - Superceded and scratch pages (for reference) (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Chapter titles (Box-folder 25/7)
    - Original “Toots” material (pre-revision) and original of re-typed copy (Box-folder 25/8)
    - College songs and stomps, marches and blues of the middle twenties (Box-folder 25/9)
    - Early notes, Asbury Park guide, etc. (Box-folder 25/10)
  - Miscellaneous lyric sheets, Titles include: Alone too much; At the old sewing circle; Beat, old heart; The birth of the beat; Brooklyn’s outa dis world; Come back my love; Design for loving; The good humor man; If you didn’t belong to me; I’m takin’ the beat to Bali; The longer I love you; Love or reason; My love was young; No love/Still no love/Now love; Oh Friday; Rapunzel, Rapunzel (let down your hair); Salute to the Admiral; Sharp as a dart; You threw me a curve (Box-folder 25/11)
- Photographs (Box 26-27)
  - Portraits of Walker (Box-folder 26/1)
  - Walker family (Box-folder 26/2)
  - Walker with others, Includes the Interfraternity Orchestra, University of Pennsylvania, and Milton Rosenstock (Box-folder 26/3)
  - Miscellaneous photographs (Box-folder 26/4)
  - Production photos from Mistress of the Inn (Box-folder 26/5)
  - Fred Waring and the largest Synco-Symphonic Orchestra in the World, Roxy Theatre, New York, Photograph rolled (Box 27)
- Music (Box 28-131)
  - Show Music (Box 28-91, 107-126)
    - Admiral Broadway revue, 1949, TV show on NBC and Dumont networks
      - Main title, Short score; Laid in: Credits and announcer text (Box-folder 28/1)
    - Allah be praised, 1944, Music by Baldwin Bergerson and Don Walker, lyrics by George Marion Jr.
      - Full scores
        - Allah be praised (Box-folder 107/1)
        - Allah be praised-continuation (Box-folder 107/2)
        - Allah be praised-Kraft sisters (Box-folder 107/3)
        - Allah be praised-Kraft Allah (new) (Box-folder 107/4)
        - Allah be praised-Tag (Box-folder 107/5)
        - Ballet finale (Box-folder 107/6)
        - Ballet finale (new) (Box-folder 107/7)
        - Emir's entrance (Box-folder 107/8)
        - Finale ultimo (Box-folder 107/9)
        - Intro to Finale ultimo (Box-folder 107/10)
        - Finaletto-Act I (Box-folder 107/11)
        - Hollywood ballet (Box-folder 107/12)
        - I was a happier man in Dannemora (Box-folder 107/13)
        - I was a happier man in Dannemora-encore (Box-folder 107/14)
        - I was a happier man in Dannemora-Intro to encore (Box-folder 107/15)
        - I'm getting oriental over you (Box-folder 107/16)
        - I'm getting oriental over you-dance (Box-folder 107/17)
        - I'm getting oriental over you-insert (Kraft entrance) (Box-folder 107/18)
        - I'm getting oriental over you-Kraft sisters (Box-folder 107/19)
        - I'm getting oriental over you-M'ladava (Box-folder 107/20)
        - Intro to entr'acte (Box-folder 107/21)
        - Katinka to Eva to Frances (Box-folder 107/22)
        - Katinka to Eva to Frances-dance (Box-folder 107/23)
        - A leaf in the wind (Box-folder 108/1-2)
        - A leaf in the wind-continuation (Box-folder 108/3)
        - Intro to A leaf in the wind (Box-folder 108/4)
        - A leaf in the wind-modulation to 8A (new) (Box-folder 108/5)
        - A leaf in the wind-new modulation (Box-folder 108/6)
        - A leaf in the wind-reprise (Box-folder 108/7)
        - A leaf in the wind-specialty (Box-folder 108/8)
        - A leaf in the wind-tag (Box-folder 108/9)
        - Let's go too far #11 (Box-folder 108/10)
        - Let's go too far #11a (Box-folder 108/11)
        - Let's go too far-exit (Box-folder 108/12)
        - Let's go too far-reprise (Box-folder 108/13)
        - The man in the moon says "no" (Box-folder 108/14)
        - Modulation to entr’acte tag (Box-folder 108/15)
        - Overture (Box-folder 108/16)
        - The Persian way of life (Box-folder 108/17)
        - The Persian way of life-dance (Box-folder 108/18)
        - The Persian way of life-tag (Box-folder 108/19)
        - Secret song (Box-folder 108/20)
        - Secret song-change (Box-folder 108/21)
        - Secret song-modulation (Box-folder 108/22)
        - Secret song-new finish (Box-folder 108/23)
        - Snake charmer (Box-folder 108/24)
        - Sunrise on sunset (2) (Box-folder 108/25)
        - Sunrise on sunset-tag (Box-folder 108/26)
        - Sunrise on sunset-tag (new) (Box-folder 108/27)
        - That brave new world, Includes what appears to be miscellaneous cut pages (Box-folder 108/28)
        - That brave new world-encore (Box-folder 108/29)
        - Waltz duet (Box-folder 108/30)
        - What's new in New York? (Box-folder 108/31)
        - What's new in New York?-dance (Box-folder 109/1)
        - What's new in New York?-encore (Box-folder 109/2)
        - What's new in New York?-rideout (Box-folder 109/3)
        - What's new in New York?-tag (2) (Box-folder 109/4)
        - A woman doesn't like you to say "no" (Box-folder 109/5)
        - Zarah's entrance (Box-folder 109/6)
        - Miscellaneous music (Box-folder 109/7)
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Allah be praised (Box-folder 28/2)
        - Ballad #1-beguine version (Box-folder 28/3)
        - Ballad #1-straight version (Box-folder 28/3)
        - Ballet-1st Act (Box-folder 28/4)
        - Baseball incidental (Box-folder 28/5)
        - Be like a leaf (Box-folder 28/6)
        - Blues incidental (Box-folder 28/7)
        - Hollywood ballet (Box-folder 28/8)
        - I was a happier man in Donnemora (Box-folder 28/9)
        - I'm getting oriental over you (Box-folder 28/10)
        - Katinka to Eva to Frances, Laid in: string parts for "insert" (Box-folder 28/11)
        - Leaf in the wind (Box-folder 28/12)
        - Let's go too far (Box-folder 28/13)
        - The man in the moon says no (Box-folder 28/14)
        - Oil! (Box-folder 28/15)
        - Opening Act I (Box-folder 28/16)
        - The Persian way of life (Box-folder 28/17)
        - The secret song (Box-folder 28/18)
        - Sunrise on sunset (Box-folder 28/19)
        - What's new in New York? (Box-folder 28/20)
        - A woman doesn't like you to say "no" (Box-folder 28/21)
        - Miscellaneous music (Box-folder 28/22)
      - Lyric sheets (Box-folder 28/23)
      - Notebook/notes (Box-folder 28/24)
    - All's well that ends, Music and lyrics by Don Walker and Buck Warnick, book by Robert Marko and Don Walker, based on H.M.S. Pinafore
      - Script (Box-folder 29/1)
    - America loves a band, No credits
      - Finale Act I, Lyric sheet/libretto (Box-folder 29/2)
    - American jubilee, 1940, Music by Arthur Schwartz, lyrics by Osacr Hammerstein II
      - Firemen's serenade, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 29/3)
    - Angel, 1978, Music by Gary Geld, lyrics by Peter Udell
      - All the comfort's of home tag rag, Piano score (Box-folder 29/4)
    - Angela, 1969, Play by Sumner Arthur Long, incidental music by Arnold Goland and Don Walker
      - Angela A-flat (Box-folder 29/5)
      - Angela II (Box-folder 29/6)
      - Angela III (Box-folder 29/7)
      - Angela knows best, Includes lead sheet, lyrics by Walker and music by Goland (Box-folder 29/8)
      - Angela knows best-parts (Box-folder 29/9)
      - Curtain Act I (Box-folder 29/10)
      - Curtain Act II (Box-folder 29/11)
      - Final curtain (Box-folder 29/12)
      - Reading letter (Box-folder 29/13)
      - The ring (Box-folder 29/14)
      - Why shouldn't I help myself (Box-folder 29/15)
      - Editing/recording notes (Box-folder 29/16)
    - Anyone can whistle, 1964, Music and lyrics by Stephen Sondheim
      - Full scores
        - Bluebird march (Box-folder 109/8)
        - Bluebird opening (Box-folder 109/9)
        - Bluebird reprise (Box-folder 109/10)
        - Cora's playoff (Box-folder 109/11)
        - Exit music/Overture part II (Box-folder 109/12)
        - Fay's monologue (Box-folder 109/13)
        - Hapgood's entrance fanfare (Box-folder 109/14)
        - Interrogation lead in (Box-folder 109/15)
        - Interrogations (parts 1-8) (Box-folder 109/16)
        - Me and my town (Box-folder 109/17)
        - Me and my town (new) (Box-folder 109/17)
        - Miracle song, Includes pages from a variant version (Box-folder 109/18)
        - Opening Act I (Box-folder 109/19)
        - Prelude Act I (Box-folder 109/20)
        - Pumping music (Box-folder 109/21)
        - Simple see Interrogations
        - Stamping music (Box-folder 109/22)
        - There won't be trumpets (Box-folder 109/23)
        - There's always a woman (Box-folder 109/24)
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Me and my town (Box-folder 29/17)
        - Miscellaneous scores and parts (Box-folder 29/18)
    - The appointment, 1969, Film directed by Sidney Lumet, music by John Barry and Don Walker
      - Full scores, 1m-1; 2m-2; 2m-3; 3m-2; 4m-1; 4m-2; 6m-2; 6m-4; 6m-5; 7m-1; 7m-2; 12m-1; 12m-2; 13m-2; 13m-3 (part I); 14m-4 (end title) (Box-folder 109/25-40)
      - Buon giorno (wild #1), Score (Box-folder 29/19)
      - Wild theme #1, Reduced score/sketch; Wild theme #2 crossed out on verso (Box-folder 29/19)
      - Do we (false exit), Piano-vocal score/sketch (Box-folder 29/20)
      - L’amour e la civetta (wild #2), Score (Box-folder 29/21)
      - Wild #2, Reduced score/sketch (Box-folder 29/21)
      - Main theme, Reduced score/lead sheet; Appears to be in John Barry's hand (Box-folder 29/22)
      - Untitled, Sketch (Box-folder 29/22)
      - Sempre n`el cor (wild #3), Score (Box-folder 29/23)
      - Wild #4, Reduced score (Box-folder 29/24)
      - Miscellaneous and unidentified music (Box-folder 29/25)
      - Music cues (Box-folder 29/26)
      - Notes (Box-folder 29/27)
    - Are musicians people?, Music, lyrics and book by Don Walker and Clay Warnick
      - Script (Box-folder 29/28)
      - Script #2 (Box-folder 29/29)
    - At home abroad, 1935, Music by Arthur Schwartz, lyrics by Howard Dietz
      - Get away from it all, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Beat the band, 1942, Music by Johnny Green, lyrics by George Marion Jr.
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Afternoon of a phoney (Box-folder 30/2)
        - America loves a band (Box-folder 30/3)
        - Break it up (Box-folder 30/4)
        - Curtain and melos Act I (Box-folder 30/5)
        - Down thru the agents: opening Act I (Box-folder 30/6)
        - Down thru the agents Vincent insert (Box-folder 30/7)
        - Ev'ry other heartbeat (Box-folder 30/8)
        - The four freedoms (Box-folder 30/9)
        - Free, cute, and size fourteen (Box-folder 30/10)
        - I'm physical, you're cultured (Box-folder 30/11)
        - Keep it casual (Box-folder 30/12)
        - Let's comb beaches (Box-folder 30/13)
        - Let's comb beaches incidental (Box-folder 30/14)
        - Let's comb beaches incidental #2 (Box-folder 30/14)
        - Men! (Box-folder 30/15)
        - Men-agitato (Box-folder 30/15)
        - Proud of you (Box-folder 30/16)
        - Proud of you (new verse) (Box-folder 30/16)
        - The steam is on the beam (Box-folder 30/17)
    - The beauty part, 1962, Play by S.J. Perelman, incidental music by Don Walker
      - Piano scores
        - The beauty part, Laid in: lyric sheets (Box-folder 30/18)
        - Entracte (Box-folder 30/18)
        - Relief theme (party) (Box-folder 30/19)
    - Bless you all, 1950, Music and lyrics by Harold Rome
      - Piano-vocal scores, unless otherwise noted
        - Be a folk singer (Box-folder 30/20)
        - Bless you all opening (Box-folder 30/21)
        - The desert flame, Piano/short score; Composed by Don Walker (Box-folder 30/22)
        - The desert flame, Full score (Box-folder 30/23)
        - I can hear it now-ballet, Piano score; Arranged by Mischa and Wesley Portnoff (Box-folder 30/24)
        - Little things (meant so much to me) (Box-folder 30/25)
        - Love letter to Manhattan (Box-folder 31/1)
        - A rose is a rose (Box-folder 31/2)
        - Summer dresses (Box-folder 31/3)
        - Summer dress utility, Full scores (2); Orchestration by Phil Lang (Box-folder 109/41)
        - Take off the coat (Box-folder 31/4)
        - You never know what hit you (when it's love) (Box-folder 31/5)
    - Brave new world, The following items were in a folder marked “Brave New World Material” and appeared to have been for a radio program; while we have found no information to confirm that Walker was involved, there was a joint CBS and WPA radio show with that title from November of 1937 through May of 1938, a period when Walker was known to work on various radio programs–we posit that this may have been one of them
      - Sketches/scores and occasional full scores, 40 items; Titles include: Airplane intro; Big intro (4); Calls; Canon; Christmas sound; Cooch; Dog act jump rope; Fancy intro; Fight music; Hot intro; Intro; Intro to choir scene; Intro–F/A&P; Intro - lively - F; Intros; Italian medley; Italian overture; Sweet intro - in F; Sweet intro–Eb; Intro-sweet-Eb; Intro-Bb-sweet; Intro in F (sweet); Sweet intro (3); Oh me oh my oh you; Hot intro in C/Well! well! well!; Japanese incidental (cherrie blossoms); Japanese incidental (Kashimer); Jap intro; Jazz stuff (2); Kabachak (3); Low intro; March variations; Minsky’s gorilla (Box-folder 31/6-7)
    - Bucks County revue, circa 1948-1953, Music mostly by Don Walker and lyrics by Mitchell Hodges
      - Piano-vocal scores, some lyric sheets and sketches included
        - The B.C.C.C. (Box-folder 31/8)
        - The bend in the river (Box-folder 31/9)
        - Bucks County buckaroo (Box-folder 31/10)
        - I get nowhere fast (Box-folder 31/11)
        - I'm the visiting nurse (Box-folder 31/12)
        - In a hospital, Missing p. 1 (Box-folder 31/13)
        - In a hospital encore, Lyric sheets only (Box-folder 31/14)
        - Little blue gate (Box-folder 31/15)
        - Sweet sensation (Box-folder 31/16)
        - Swing thing (Box-folder 31/17)
        - What's new? (Box-folder 31/18)
        - When a psychiatric social worker falls in love (Box-folder 31/19)
        - Miscellaneous and unidentified music (Box-folder 31/20)
        - Reverse transparencies (Box-folder 31/21)
        - Lyric sheets (Box-folder 31/22)
      - Notes (Box-folder 31/23)
    - A burst of summer, A comedy by A. B. Shiffrins
      - Script (Box-folder 31/24)
    - Buttrio square, 1952, Music by Fred Stammer, lyrics by Gen Genovese
      - The Tarantura, Full score (Box-folder 31/25)
    - Carousel, 1945, Music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Piano-vocal scores, unless otherwise noted
        - Blow high, blow low (Box-folder 32/1)
        - Carousel waltz, Piano score (Box-folder 32/2)
        - Finale Act I new, Short score/sketches (Box-folder 32/3)
        - The highest judge of all (Box-folder 32/4)
        - June is bustin’ out all over, Act one scene three opening (Box-folder 32/5)
        - June is bustin' out all over dance, Short score/sketches (Box-folder 32/6)
        - Mister Snow (Box-folder 32/7)
        - Mister Snow reprise, Short score/sketches (Box-folder 32/8)
        - A real nice clambake, Short score/sketch and vocal arrangement (Box-folder 32/9)
        - Soliloquy (Box-folder 32/10)
        - What's the use of wondrin'/Geraniums/Stone cutters (Box-folder 32/11)
        - When the children are asleep (Box-folder 32/12)
        - You'll never walk alone (Box-folder 32/13)
        - Finale Act I new, Short score/sketches (Box-folder 32/3)